<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anugraha A</title>
    <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anugraha A</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Anugraha</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anugrahaambily.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Antibiotics</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/antibiotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/antibiotics/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot; Drug resistance imposes huge costs on health systems and is taking a growing-and unnecessary-toll in lives and threatening to roll back much of the progress we have made&amp;rdquo; - Ban Ki-moon
What is antibiotic resistance? How does one develop antibiotic resistance?
Do you remember taking an Amoxicillin pill for the very first time, and how better you felt in an hour? If you still feel the same after taking those, you should be happy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tale of water treatment</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/tale-of-water-treatment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/tale-of-water-treatment/</guid>
      <description>This work is my first try with comics. In this project we developed a system which produces Hydrogen Peroxide through Oxygen Reduction Reaction. We used this system for waste water treatment where contaminants with long Carbon chains were broken down and the COD was found to reduce after treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio Processing</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/audio-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/audio-processing/</guid>
      <description>This work was prepared as cover for the official website of a PhD student at Queen&amp;rsquo;s Mary University, London. His work is mainly focused on audio processing. Imagine you are standing in the middle of a street in a city. close your eyes= what do you hear? Perhaps car..bus..footsteps..beeps&amp;hellip;human speech&amp;hellip;music &amp;hellip; siren..??Your sense of hearing tells you what is happening around you, without any sense of vision, right?! How do computers/mobile gadgets make sense of these urban sounds - &amp;ldquo;machine listening&amp;rdquo; and then how could we make use of machine listening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover for “Surface Science and Interface Engineering” group</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/surface-eng-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/surface-eng-cover/</guid>
      <description>This work was prepared as a cover for the official website of Dr T N Narayanan&amp;rsquo;s research group in which I am also included as a Junior Research Fellow. Our research focus is on the development of functional mesoscopic interfaces, and probing the novel and unprecedented phenomena emanating from these junctions. Development of novel interfaces from 1D, 2D and 3D nanomaterials is one of the key research focuses. Interface induced heterogeneous catalysis control is another core theme of our research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INSA - Serb Science image and film competition</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/insa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/insa/</guid>
      <description>This work was done to participate in the Insa - Serb Science image and film competition, where the topic was &#39; Science through my eyes&amp;rsquo;. Science connects a wide variety of fields and continents through various discoveries. Science is an answer to the never ending mysteries. It has always been the ultimate solution to any problems and is a superhero who serves the world. From fire to most recent discoveries in artificial intelligence, it has always made our life simpler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum material on catalysis</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/cover-quantum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/cover-quantum/</guid>
      <description>This work was prepared as a cover for an upcoming journal on Quantum materials for catalysis. Some of the materials such as Perovskites, defective Graphene oxide, Molybdenum disulfide, Mexene etc with interesting electronic and topological properties, are used in different applications in various catalyst</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schematic Representation to show Cu based catalysts for electrochemical Carbon dioxide reduction process</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/cu-based-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/cu-based-catalyst/</guid>
      <description>This work was done as a schematic representation for &amp;lsquo;3D printing of bio-inspired porous graphene based composite reinforced with Cu based catalyst for CO2 conversion.&amp;rsquo; In the current project, graphene as well as graphene-hexagonal boron nitride based structurally reinforced composite will be printed into the porous blocks with low density, high strength, and high surface area architecture, which can be used as template for embedding Cu based catalysts for electrochemical CO2 reduction process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOC for paper on hydrogen peroxide generation</title>
      <link>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/toc-hyd-peroxide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anugrahaambily.github.io/portfolio/toc-hyd-peroxide/</guid>
      <description>This was designed as a TOC for a paper on &#39; Electrochemically derived functionalized graphene for bulk production of hydrogen peroxide&amp;rsquo;. Oxidized graphitic carbon-based materials have been recently proposed as an alternative to metal-based catalysts in the electrochemical oxygen reduction reaction (ORR), and in this work we unravel the role of C=O groups in graphene towards sustainable peroxide formation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>